ATU PROSPER

Software Engineer

PROFILE

I am a smart-working Software Engineer with a flair for creating elegant and quality solutions in the possible least amount of time. I specialize in full-stack web development using JavaScript. I can plan and design a good Software Architecture, choosing the best Patterns.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2016 ABIA STATE POLYTECHNIC, ABA **HND - COMPUTER SCIENCE**

EXPERIENCE

2020 - 2021 **METROVATECH**

WEB DEVELOPER

- Design wordpress websites for clients
- Plan and develop full stack web applications using MongoDB/MySQL/PostgresSQL, Node JS, Express JS, React JS, Next JS and Typescript

2018 - 2020 CODELAB PROJECTS

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER/ **GRAPHICS DESIGNER**

- Designing of flyers and other printable materials
- Design wordpress websites for clients

SKILLS

- HTML CSS
- Express JS
- Javascript
- React JS
- Next JS

- Typescript
- Firebase
- Wordpress
- Gatsby JS
- Node JS Jest

- Tailwind CSS
- Material-UI
- Redux
- Strapi
- GraphQL
- REST API

- Version Control
- Corel Draw
- Illustrator
- Photoshop

PROJECTS/PORTFOLIO

Clients Project

- www.punterscompanion.com
- www.thetantalizersca.com
- www.gtafricanmart.ca
- www.chappelledaycare.ca
- www.moorfieldoptometry.com.ng

Personal Projects

- www.punterscompanion.com
- www.thetantalizersca.com
- www.gtafricanmart.ca
- www.chappelledaycare.ca
- www.welloilmaf.com

Hobbies

Watch soccer





ডি Watch comedy skits